#### Contact

banks\_kayleigh@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kayleighbanks-rn (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Nursing

**ACLS** 

**Patient Safety** 

#### Certifications

Registered Nurse

Registered nurse

Registered Nurse

# Kayleigh Banks

Emergency Services Assistant Manager at PeaceHealth Bellingham, Washington

# Summary

I am a passionate Registered Nurse with 11 years of diverse nursing experience.

I have an extensive Emergency background.

My experiences as a travel nurse showcase my adaptability and willingness to learn new skills.

I am dedicated to providing high-quality, evidence-based, patientcentered care with every encounter.

TNCC, ENPC, PALS, BLS, ACLS

# Experience

PeaceHealth

2 years 5 months

Emergency Services Assistant Manager March 2020 - Present (5 months)

Bellingham, Washington

#### Registered Nurse

November 2019 - March 2020 (5 months)

Bellingham, Washington Area

**Emergency Department RN** 

#### Registered Nurse

March 2018 - November 2019 (1 year 9 months)

Sedro-Woolley, WA

Registered Nurse in Surgical Services of a Critical Access Hospital. I worked in the Pre-operative, PACU, Phase II recovery, and Endoscopy areas. I floated to the Emergency Department and the medical/surgical unit as needed. I also worked as relief Nurse Team Lead (charge RN) in both Surgical Services and the ED, as well as relief nursing supervisor for the hospital.

Bellingham Ambulatory Surgery Center Per diem PACU RN September 2018 - April 2020 (1 year 8 months) Bellingham, Washington Area

WhidbeyHealth Medical Center
Travel RN
November 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 4 months)
Coupeville, WA

I successfully completed a travel assignment at this Level III Trauma

Emergency Department. During my time there I was used as a charge RN

frequently, and adapted quickly to the role. I was used routinely in the role of
triage. I was also used to orient both new hires and new travelers to the unit.

Dameron Hospital Association Travel RN August 2016 - November 2016 (4 months) Stockton, California Area

I successfully worked as an Emergency Department travel RN with three days orientation in this extremely busy ED in an often violent and low-income area. I was often used in the role of triage, where I was able to successfully monitor the flow of the department as well as ensuring that people received timely and adequate care based on my assessment of their presenting health concerns.

MultiCare Health System
Travel Nurse
May 2016 - August 2016 (4 months)
Tacoma. WA

I successfully completed a challenging assignment in this large, busy, urban Level II Trauma Center with limited orientation.

University of Washington Medical Center Travel Nurse February 2016 - May 2016 (4 months) Seattle, WA

I was a member of the Acute Care Resource Team on this travel nurse assignment. I floated to several different departments including Oncology, telemetry, the Emergency Department, surgical departments, rehabilitation and pre/post-transplant departments. I was able to successfully adapt to each of these departments with less than a shift of orientation in each.

Cape Cod Healthcare Travel Nurse May 2015 - January 2016 (9 months) Falmouth, MA

I did a repeat travel nurse assignment in this seasonally extremely busy, rural emergency department. I often was assigned the triage role and was a trusted member of the team.

Adventist Health System
Travel Nurse at White Memorial Medical Center
February 2015 - May 2015 (4 months)
Los Angeles, CA

I worked as a travel Emergency Department RN in this extremely busy East Los Angeles Level III trauma center. I worked closely with an underserved immigrant population, as well as in an area known for tremendous amounts of gang violence. I was used frequently in the triage and "first eyes" role.

St. Francis Hospital
Travel RN in the ER
November 2014 - February 2015 (4 months)
Wilmington Delaware

I successfully completed an assignment in this city ED known for dealing with an underserved population, as well as being in a dangerous area. Common patient complaints included trauma and injury secondary acts of violence.

Cape Cod Healthcare
Travel RN
August 2014 - November 2014 (4 months)
Falmouth MA

I worked as a travel RN for an extremely seasonally busy emergency department in Cape Cod, MA.

Johns Hopkins Bayview Medical Center Travel RN May 2014 - August 2014 (4 months)

This was my first assignment as a travel nurse. I worked in the Emergency Department of the Bayview campus of this nationally known and prestigious institution. The Bayview campus is a Level II trauma center. I was able to adapt within three shifts of orientation to my new role as a travel nurse in one

of America's most dangerous cities and one of the most prestigious facilities in the world, despite never working in a city or a trauma center in the past.

## Milford Regional Medical Center

RN

November 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 7 months)

I worked as a staff emergency department RN in the busiest facility between Boston, MA and Worcester, MA. I was often used in the triage capacity and was given a 13-week critical care course by this facility as well as many months on the job training.

Take Care Health Systems
Occupational Health Nurse
October 2012 - May 2014 (1 year 8 months)
Intel - Hudson, MA

I worked at a single staffed occupational health clinic within an Intel factory.

## MetroWest Medical Center

RN

August 2008 - June 2013 (4 years 11 months)

Framingham, MA

I worked as an RN on both a medical/surgical/orthopedics floor and a floor that specialized more in surgical oncology.

## Education

Spring Arbor University
MSN/MBA, MSN/MBA Dual Degree · (2019 - 2022)

Nebraska Methodist College BSN, Nursing · (2016 - 2019)

### Becker College

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2006 - 2008)